In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
Now...
...you are mine.
I don't give a damn about you.
The rear guard will be...
Guts...
I want you to do it.
Now it's my job to take care of the rest!
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
The Hand of God
Hey, you're up early.
You really like high places, don't you?
So? What's your take on us?
What do you mean?
You think it's the place for you?
I don't know yet.
It's different here...
Everybody's the same
in ordinary mercenary bands.
It's easy to see their ranks are full of
hoodlums and men with shady pasts.
But I think something's different here...
I wonder if that's true...
If I had to explain why,
I would say it's Griffith.
Everyone sincerely admires Griffith...
Everyone expects great things
to come from staying with Griffith...
To sum up, these men have gathered
because of Griffith's charisma.
Of course, it's kill or be killed...
We fight in bloody battles every day...
...but strange as it sounds,
we can live like normal people here.
What kind of guy is Griffith really?
I don't know.
Now, now, listen...
I can't really describe it, but...
I think Griffith believes in something
beyond swordsmanship and tactics.
It's probably beyond his reach to turn
his belief into reality in one lifetime.
That's what he has.
His belief?
In what?
In everything.
Hey, rookie!
Griffith's calling you!
See ya.
Guts!
I bet you'll find it right here...
...the place where you belong.
Hey!
What do you say? Join me!
There's nothing better for a hangover.
I'm fine.
Oh, come on, don't be shy.
Cut it out! We're not kids,
for crying out loud!
What a funny face!
Nice try!
Awfully feisty for so early in the day.
That was some good morning exercise.
Guts, you...
Now we're even.
All right, I surrender.
You are entirely too thickheaded.
Oh, this?
I got this from an old
fortune-teller woman long ago.
The behelit...
This is also known as the Egg of the King...
...for once you possess this,
you are destined to rule the world...
...in exchange for your flesh and blood.
Rule the world?
Catch!
I don't know how it works though...
It looks alive, doesn't it?
It's creepy...
Isn't it fascinating?
I didn't hear your answer yet.
Why did you come back
to help me during that battle?
I didn't want to lose an outstanding
warrior like you in such trivial battle.
I put in so much work to get you.
Guts...
You should come along with me.
Now we've taken only a step...
The Band of the Hawk itself...
Victory in several battles...
It's merely the first step, just the beginning.
The real fun for us has yet to come...
...and we're ready to risk our lives for it.
I will have my own kingdom.
You must fight for me...
...because you belong to me.
I will choose the place
where you will die for me.
Have his own kingdom?
He's not nobility or royalty,
much less a knight...
He's no more than the leader of
a mercenary band of 500 or so...
But he talks as if all that is his right...
The enemy numbers about a thousand.
The first unit leads, while
the second and third cover the flanks!
First unit, charge!
What have I really been
doing for the past four years?
Guts!
Give me my spear!
Be quick about it!
Don't be so damn slow!
Do you want to get me killed?
Gambino...
Come on, what are you doing?
Hey, Guts, why not use a smaller
sword, one right for your size?
Never!
You thickheaded brat!
We don't carry any swords
for kids here anyway!
Is it true the kid was born from a corpse?
Yeah, Gambino's wife, Shisu, found him.
That's a sign of bad luck...
Then it was probably
his fault Shisu died, right?
It's only when I wielded this that I didn't
have to think about anything else.
To the victor go all the spoils!
Hey, Guts!
It's your first real battle. Work hard.
Charge!
Gambino!
Watch your ass!
This is not a swordplay lesson!
Don't act like an idiot
just because you took one down!
Next!
Gambino!
What's up?
Look!
Here you go.
Well, keep it up.
Yeah!
Go!
We're close!
Charge!
Gambino!
Gambino, look at this!
I got the enemy commander!
I won the whole reward!
What about meat?
Meat...
...to feed him.
O-Okay...
What is it?
Just bring me the meat...
Bring it right now!
I'll go get it.
He's got it good, our Gambino!
We should all follow his example.
Hey, what did you say?
What the hell did you say?
J-Just kidding...
Gambino?
G-Gambino...
It's unlike me to be so careless...
I expected you to drop dead long ago.
You should be dead, bastard...
And what happened?
Shisu, who found you,
dropped dead instead...
And now I'm in this miserable condition...
This is like a joke!
What do you have against me?
You return good with evil!
Gambino, I...
You're a son of the devil.
A doomed child raised under an evil sign...
You were the one who deserved to die...
...on that day eleven years ago...
...beneath your mother's body...
You should have died!
You were never more than a pest.
I hated you, following me around
like a dog after you killed Shisu.
You...
...should have died!
Y-You killed...
Shisu...
G-Gambino...
Gam...
What's wrong? Night raid?
Guts!
What the hell is going on here?
Don't tell me you did this...
You, answer me!
You did it...
Wait!
This isn't...
You'll pay for this!
Get him!
What happened?
What the...
It's Guts!
That kid just killed Gambino!
You've got to be kidding!
It's true!
The kid just bit the hand that
fed him for more than ten years!
It's no different than murdering his father!
Why?
Why did this happen?
Wait!
You murderer!
Did we get him?
Yeah, I think so.
Falling from this height
would mean certain death anyway.
Either way, Gambino will never
be able to rest in the afterlife.
I can't move...
My body is frozen...
Will I die here...
Will I...
Where am I going?
If I had stayed
back there, I'd be better off...
If I were dead back there...
There would be nothing more...
But now bad things are waiting...
Where...
It's the end...
The end...
Yes, this is...
I have not changed at all from back then...
Just killing enemies...
...only to survive...
Where do I want to go?
Where...
Hey, are you still alive?
Yeah, I think so.
You have the devil's own luck,
no matter what you do.
Here...
On the battlefield, a soldier's life
is worth no more than a silver coin.
As if it were nothing...
...most men's lives are controlled
by a handful of nobles and royalty.
Well, even a king is really unable
to live his life as he pleases...
We're all just surrendering to
the flow that is known as fate...
Then we fade away.
Our lives are squandered,
and we don't know who we are.
There must be a man who's born with
the leverage to change the world...
...regardless of social status or class.
That man would be part of
this world's true privileged class.
That man could have
the absolute power of a god!
I must know...
...what my status really is in this world!
What has been preordained for me in this life?
It's strange...
I've never told this
to anyone else before, only you.
Mr. Guts!
What's your problem?
I just wanted to congratulate you.
Mr. Guts, I heard you were
promoted to raider commander.
It's amazing. You only have
two weeks of experience.
It's no big deal at all.
Anyway...
You've become one of us for real!
Congratulations!
Just call me Guts.
Pippin!
Look, we fell!
You should be careful!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
In days long past,
beyond one's distant memories...
...man has shielded the tiny wounds
in his heart by picking up a sword.
In days yet to come,
beyond one's distant hopes...
...man will wield a sword so
that he may smile upon his journey.
A kingdom in the west
and an empire in the east.
The war between Midland and Tudor
has lasted one hundred years.
During the war,
the Grim Reapers of the Battlefield...
...the Band of the Hawk...
...increased their power greatly,
fighting on the side of Midland.
Three years have passed...
Charge, charge!
Tear them apart!
We, the Black Ram Heavy Cavalry...
...must lend our courage
to the entire empire!
Kill them all!
Crush them to pieces!
I can barely watch my men!
They are thrown into confusion by
an army of only three thousand men!
Due to our foes' onslaught,
we've endured immense damage!
We'll be cut off from the castle!
I ask for anyone's help...
I beseech anyone who can stop
the march of Tudor's black devils...
Charge, charge!
What nonsense!
Fighting against us all by himself?
All right!
We'll shatter your bones!
D-Don't break up your formation!
Only one soldier is against us!
Encircle him!
Cut off his movements!
T-They are...
Your Majesty, look!
T-The Band of the Hawk!
The Grim Reapers of the Battlefield
led by the White Hawk, Griffith!
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...